<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharon Zheng</title>
    <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sharon Zheng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:02:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhenghxy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Luminescent Membrane Sensor Design</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/3projectdescription/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/3projectdescription/</guid>
      <description>Luminescent Membrane Sensor Design  Mar. 2017 to Jul. 2018
 Project Report
    Synthesized the membrane sensor and tested for its stability, luminescence sensing and sensing mechanism within experimental groups and control groups.
  Visualized the experiment data and finished the paper with other 6 teammates; had the result published on Journal of Photochemistry and Photobiology A: Chemistry, vol. 370, February 2019, pp. 51&amp;ndash;57. doi: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Forecast for 2020 Net Export</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/2projectdescription/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/2projectdescription/</guid>
      <description>Time Series Forecast for Net Export  Sep. to Nov. 2020
 Project Report
    Used Akaike Criterion to determine an Autoregressive Distributed Lag model with lagged values of 5 leading indicators, and conducted Forecast Combination with Granger-Ramanathan Combination Test.
  Visualized the stability of coefficients by parallel Rolling and Recursive Estimation and added break points with statistical evidence of Chow test; checked the unbiasedness of the model through Mincer-Zarnowitz Test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monte-Carlo Simulation Modeling</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/1projectdescription/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/projects/1projectdescription/</guid>
      <description>New York Upstate Helicopter Emergency Transportation Modeling  Sep. to Dec. 2021
 Project Report
    Completed a simulation analysis of helicopter transport operations in the upstate New York area to help determine how many helicopters are needed and where they should be based.
  Conducted empirical data analysis and fitted the input data for the distributions that are used in the simulation process.
  Optimized the number of helicopters should be employed and locations of bases to minimize the average response time given the results from the model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/about-me/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:01:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/about-me/description/</guid>
      <description>Hongxueyang (Sharon) Zheng  Hometown: Tsingtao, China/ Richmond, TX Undergrad Institutes: Sun Yat-sen University (Gunagzhou, China)/ University of Wisconsin-Madison (Madison, WI) Master&amp;rsquo;s Institute: Cornell University (Ithaca, NY) Majors I have taken: Material Science and Engineering; Mathematics; Economics; Financial Engineering Future Field: Financial Quantitative Analysis; Crypto; High Frequency Trading Contact Info:  email: hz295@cornell.edu
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:01:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/description/</guid>
      <description>Hongxueyang (Sharon) Zheng Hometown: Tsingtao  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Courses</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/courses/selectedcourses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:01:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/courses/selectedcourses/</guid>
      <description>Selected Coursework: Math: Optimization, Number Theory, Mathematical Analysis, Game Theory, Stochastic Calculus;
Coding &amp;amp; Analysis: Simulation Modeling and Analysis, Monte Carlo Methods in Financial Engineering, Machine Learning for Data Science, Big Data Technology, Statistics for Financial Engineering;
Finance: Derivatives Securities, Investment&amp;amp;Portfolio Management, Financial Statement Analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://zhenghxy.github.io/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 17:40:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhenghxy.github.io/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description>Download Resume
Hongxueyang (Sharon) Zheng EDUCATION Cornell University, College of Engineering, Ithaca, NY&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;Expected December 2022
Master of Engineering in Financial Engineering
University of Wisconsin-Madison, Madison, WI&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;December 2020
Bachelor of Science in Mathematics &amp;amp; Economics (Double Major),
Graduation with Distinction, GPA: 3.97
Sun Yat-sen University, Guangzhou, China&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;July 2018
Bachelor of Science in Materials Science and Engineering
Selected Coursework: Optimization, Simulation Modeling and Analysis, Machine Learning for Data Science, Monte Carlo Methods in Financial Engineering, Number Theory, Derivatives Securities, Portfolio Management, Financial Statement Analysis</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
